This is my ticket to Star Wars.
(Sheldon:)I don't have to tell you
it is worth far more
(Sheldon:)than its face value
of $15.50.
(Sheldon:)I trust you'll give it
to someone worthy.
(Leonard:)You got it.
(Leonard:)Well, Penny might
want to join us.
(Sheldon:)This is my ticket
to Star Wars.
(knocking)
SHELDON: Penny.
Penny?
(knocking)
(Bernadette:)What happens if
I say, “Come in”?
(Penny:)Well, find out.
Come in!
(knocking)
Bernadette?
(knocking) Bernadette?
Come in!
SHELDON:
Keep it up.
(Sheldon:)I got nowhere else to be.
(Bernadette:)Just come in.
(Sheldon:)For future reference,
if I want to watch Mean Girls,
(Sheldon:)I'll stream it on Netflix.
(Penny:)We're sorry.
What do you need?
(Sheldon:)Well, as you know,
(Sheldon:)I'll be celebrating
Amy's birthday with her,
(Sheldon:)and I could use your assistance
(Sheldon:)in helping me select
the perfect gift.
(Raj:)Sure.
Well, so far,